Create Account
--------------

Site ID code:   

Login
-----

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Username: |     |
| Password: |     |
|     |

Forgot Your Username Or Password?
---------------------------------

 Your email address:   

  1-888-463-2247[Take survey](http://www.surveymonkey.com/s/HQ82PVX)

Create account Log in

Terms and Privacy Policy
========================

TERMS AND CONDITIONS
--------------------

Welcome to www.eurekaexpress.org. Our website goal is to provide you with access to comprehensive career information, including: colleges and universities, programs of study, self-assessment tools and occupation descriptions. We also aim to provide a wide selection of services, books, and other products. Our Terms and Privacy Policy details what you can expect from us and what we expect from you. The use of this site is governed by the policies, terms, and conditions set forth below. Please read them carefully. If you visit, join, shop, or place an order at this site, you accept these terms and conditions.

SHARING OF LOG-IN NAME AND PASSWORD
-----------------------------------

You are responsible for safeguarding the use of your individual Log In Name and Password. You may not permit another person or entity to use your individual Log In Name and Password. In the event it is discovered that another person or entity is using your individual Log In Name or Password, EUREKA has the sole right and discretion to terminate your Subscription immediately.

COPYRIGHT AND TRADEMARK NOTICE
------------------------------

Unless otherwise specified, all materials appearing on this site, including text, logos, graphics, icons, images, and the site design as well as the selection, assembly, and arrangement are the sole property of EUREKA, the California Career Information System (EUREKA); and are protected by United States and international copyright laws. You are hereby granted a non-exclusive license to view and print the contents of www.eurekaexpress.org (the "Content") for your personal use only. Commercial use of any of the Content is strictly prohibited. You may not display www.eurekaexpress.org in frames (or any of the Content via in-line links) without the express written permission of EUREKA. Except as expressly provided herein, all rights are reserved.

LIMITED WARRANTY; LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
-----------------------------------------

You expressly agree that your use of www.eurekaexpress.org is at your own risk. Neither EUREKA, nor its affiliates, nor any of its officers, directors, or employees, agents, third-party content providers, merchants, sponsors, licensors, or the like warrant that your use of www.eurekaexpress.org will be uninterrupted or error-free; nor do they make any warranty as to the results that may be obtained from your use of www.eurekaexpress.org, or as to the accuracy, reliability, or currency of any information, Content, service, or merchandise offered or provided through www.eurekaexpress.org.

www.eurekaexpress.org AND THE CONTENT THEREOF ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS," "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF TITLE, MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. NO ORAL ADVICE OR WRITTEN INFORMATION GIVEN BY EUREKA OR ITS AFFILIATES, OR ANY OF ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, PROVIDERS, MERCHANTS, SPONSORS, LICENSORS, OR THE LIKE SHALL CREATE A WARRANTY; NOR SHALL YOU RELY ON ANY SUCH INFORMATION OR ADVICE. IF EUREKA CANNOT LAWFULLY DISCLAIM IMPLIED WARRANTIES UNDER THIS LIMITED WARRANTY, ALL SUCH WARRANTIES, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF TITLE, MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT, ARE LIMITED TO THE FULL EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW. SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW DISCLAIMER OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES AND/OR LIMITATIONS ON HOW LONG IMPLIED WARRANTY LASTS, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. THIS WARRANTY GIVES YOU SPECIFIC LEGAL RIGHTS, AND YOU MAY ALSO HAVE OTHER RIGHTS, WHICH VARY FROM STATE TO STATE.

UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL EUREKA, ITS AFFILIATES OR ANY OF THEIR RESPECTIVE OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, PROVIDERS, MERCHANTS, SPONSORS, LICENSORS, OR ANY OTHER PARTY INVOLVED IN CREATING, PRODUCING, OR DISTRIBUTING www.eurekaexpress.org BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES THAT RESULT FROM YOUR USE OR INABILITY TO USE www.eurekaexpress.org, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO YOUR RELIANCE ON ANY CONTENT OR OTHER INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM www.eurekaexpress.org OR THAT RESULTS FROM MISTAKES, OMISSIONS, INTERRUPTIONS, DELETION OF FILES OR E-MAIL, ERRORS, DEFECTS, VIRUSES, DELAYS IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, OR ANY FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, WHETHER OR NOT RESULTING FROM ACTS OF GOD, COMMUNICATIONS FAILURE, THEFT, DESTRUCTION, OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO www.eurekaexpress.org'S RECORDS, PROGRAMS, OR SERVICES, EVEN IF EUREKA WAS AWARE OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. YOU HEREBY ACKNOWLEDGE THAT THIS SECTION SHALL APPLY TO ALL CONTENT, MERCHANDISE, AND SERVICES AVAILABLE THROUGH www.eurekaexpress.org. SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.

RIGHTS
------

EUREKA reserves the right to remove any content that it deems in its sole discretion to be a violation of any law or of these Terms and Conditions. EUREKA may elect to electronically monitor the user-submit areas and may disclose any content, records, or electronic communication of any kind (i) to satisfy any law, regulation, or government request; (ii) if such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to operate www.eurekaexpress.org; or (iii) to protect the rights or property of EUREKA, its users, sponsors, providers, licensers, or merchants.

EUREKA is not responsible for screening, policing, editing, or monitoring such content. If notified of allegedly infringing, defamatory, damaging, illegal, or offensive content, EUREKA may investigate the allegation and determine in its sole discretion whether to remove or request the removal of such content from www.eurekaexpress.org. Neither EUREKA, nor its affiliates, nor any of their respective officers, directors, employees, or agents, nor any provider, merchant, sponsor, or licensor shall assume liability for any action or inaction with respect to conduct, communication, or content on www.eurekaexpress.org.

ONLINE CONDUCT
--------------

Any conduct by you that in EUREKA's sole discretion restricts or inhibits any other user from using www.eurekaexpress.org is strictly prohibited. You agree to use www.eurekaexpress.org only for lawful purposes. All users are prohibited from posting on or transmitting through www.eurekaexpress.org any unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, sexually explicit, profane, hateful, racially, ethnically, or otherwise objectionable material of any kind, including but not limited to any material that encourages conduct that would constitute a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability, or otherwise violate any applicable local, state, national, or international law.

PRIVACY POLICY
--------------

We recognize that our customers' personally identifiable information deserves protection. This privacy policy applies to all information collected or submitted on [www.eurekaexpress.org](http://www.eurekaexpress.org/).

On some pages of www.eurekaexpress.org, you can order products, make requests or register to receive materials. The types of personally identifiable information collected on these pages may include your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, and credit/debit card information. EUREKA maintains commercially reasonable safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of your personally identifiable information.

EUREKA uses this information to fulfill your requests for certain products, services and materials, and to contact you about specials and new products. In order to do so, EUREKA may disclose certain of your personally identifiable information to necessary third parties **only**. This may include without limitation, credit card processing companies and shipping companies.

Under no circumstances does EUREKA, CCIS sell your private information to any concerns.
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

EUREKA may amend its privacy policy from time to time without advance notice to you. If EUREKA decides to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, EUREKA will notify you by way of an email. You will have a choice as to whether or not EUREKA may use your information in this different manner. Otherwise, EUREKA will use all personally identifiable information only in accordance with the privacy policy in effect when such information was collected. Notwithstanding the foregoing sentence, EUREKA reserves the right to use your personally identifiable information in cooperation with any state, local, and federal officials in any investigation relating to any Content (including personal or private electronic communication transmitted on www.eurekaexpress.org) or purported unlawful activities of any user.

Our Features
------------

* [### Self-Assessment
    
    Discover yourself.](https://www.eurekaexpress.org/express/pub_assessments.asp)
* [### Career & Education Exploration
    
    Choose your destination.](https://www.eurekaexpress.org/express/pub_careers_edu.asp)
* [### Personal Development Tools
    
    Putting it all together.](https://www.eurekaexpress.org/express/pub_dev_plan.asp)

© 2022 EUREKA, CCIS
